(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-10T22:29:27.034538",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Long ago, the heavenly Realm was governed by the gods of light and order.
The Human Realm, the Demon Realm, and the Heavenly Realm...
...all worlds were kept in balance by the Celestial Lake of Light.
A sacred \"law\" forbade any from entering the lake or sullying its waters.
Long ago, the heavenly Realm was governed by the gods of light and order.
The Human Realm, the Demon Realm, and the Heavenly Realm.
All worlds were kept in balance by the Celestial Lake of Light.
A sacred law forbade any from entering the lake or sullying its waters.
The goddess Kronii was spending her days joyfully in the heavens.
A mischievous girl, today, too, she was chasing after her friends...
...playing pranks and teasing them. She was a bit of a scatterbrained deity.
Another beautiful day...
Weather like this really makes me want to sing!
せまい せまい
Narrow, narrow...
せまい あなぼこで
...inside a narrow hole...
夢を見せあう ぼくたちは
...the two of us show each other our dreams.
あの世も この世も いられない
We can't be in that world, neither can we be in this world.
あの世も この世も いられない や
ああ 神様 子どもの神様
Dear god - the god of children...
ぼくらは あなたの遊んだ
...we are inside the sandbox where you amused yourself...
砂場の中で
...inside the sandbox...
すり傷だらけです
...and we are covered in scratches.
踊るよ
We dance,
回るよ
we spin around.
僕らの踊りはおかしな踊り
Our dance is a queer one.
踊ったつもりで 笑ったつもりで
We thought we were dancing, we thought we were laughing...
倒れたつもりで 叫んだつもり
...we thought we were falling over, we thought we were screaming.
目がふらふら 音もふにゃふにゃ
Our eyes are shaky, all sounds are a jumble.
足もふらふら マボロシふにゃふにゃ
Our legs are also shaky, an illusion, a jumble.
太陽も 月も 空も 神さまも
The sun, the moon, the sky, and god -
生み出して
bringing forth this life...
あなぐらぐらしは
...of hole-dwelling.
抜け出せない
We can't escape.
抜け出せないから
We can't escape, so...
抜け出さない
...we won't escape.
抜け出さないから
We won't escape, so...
お目目閉じて
...close your eyes.
2、1、0
2, 1, 0...
落ちて 落ちて 落ちてゆこうよ
Let's fall, let's fall, let's fall and fall...
あなぐらぐらしの渦の中
...into the vortex of this life of hole-dwelling.
落ちて 落ちて 落ちてゆこうよ
Let's fall, let's fall, let's fall and fall together...
いっしょに仲良くどこまでも
...like the best of friends, wherever it may take us.
おんなじ おんなじ おんなじじゃないか
The same, the same, the same, are we not?
きみと僕とは いつまでも
You and me, forever and always.
おんなじ おんなじ おんなじじゃないか
The same, the same, the same, are we not?
いけない いけない さみしい さみしい
It's wrong, so wrong, but we're lonely, so lonely.
落ちて 落ちて
Let's fall, let's fall,
落ちてゆこうよ
...let's fall and fall.
ラララ...
Lalala...
落ちて 落ちて
Let's fall, let's fall,
落ちてゆこうよ
...let's fall and fall.
ラララ...
Lalala...
おんなじ おんなじ おんなじじゃないか
Are we not all the same, the same, the same?
ラララ...
Lalala...
おんなじ おんなじ おんなじじゃないか
Are we not all the same, the same, the same?
いけない いけない さみしい さみしい
It's wrong, so wrong, but we're lonely, so lonely.
なかま なかま あなたは いかが？
One of us, one of us, what do you say?
なかま なかま ぼくらは なかま
One of us, one of us, we're all in this together.
あなたは なかま？ 合言葉？
Are you one of us? What's the password?
あなぐらせかいの 合言葉？
The password for this world of holes?
抜け出せない 抜け出せない
We can't escape, we can't escape.
抜け出せないから 教えない
We can't escape, so we won't tell you.
あなたは なかま？ さみしい なかま？
Are you one of us? One of us lonely folks?
奈落に生きる なかま ですか？
Are you one of us inhabitants of the pit of hell?
夢を かけらを 飲んでいる
We're drinking up the dreams - every last fragment of them,
きみの夢も まぜまぜ していて
...gonna mix your dream in, too.
あの世も この世も いられない
We can't be in that world, neither can we be in this world.
目が ふらふら 音も ふにゃふにゃ
Our eyes are shaky, all sounds are a mere jumble,
腕も ふらふら マボロシ ふにゃふにゃ
...our arms are also shaky, an illusion, a mere jumble.
太陽も 月も 空も 神さまも
The sun, the moon, the sky, and god...
ギトギトに 鮮やかで
...so unctuously vibrant, all of them.
抜け出せない 抜け出せない
We can't escape, we can't escape.
抜け出せないから 抜け出さない
We can't escape, so we won't escape.
抜け出さないから お目目 閉じて
We won't escape, so close your eyes...
閉じて 閉じて 閉じて...
...close your eyes, close them, close them...
ルルル...
Lalala...
アア...
Ah...
落ちて 落ちて 落ちてゆこうよ
Let's fall, let's fall, let's fall, and fall,
あなぐらぐらしの 渦の中
...into the vortex of this life of hole-dwelling.
落ちて 落ちて 落ちてゆこうよ
Let's fall, let's fall, let's fall, and fall together,
いっしょに 仲良く どこまでも
...like the best of friends, wherever it may take us.
おんなじ おんなじ おんなじじゃないか
Are we not all the same, the same, the same?
きみと 僕とは いつまでも
You and me, forever and always,
おんなじ おんなじ おんなじじゃないか
...are we not all the same, the same, the same?
いけない いけない さみしい さみしい
It's wrong, so wrong, but we're lonely, so lonely.
落ちて 落ちて 落ちてゆこうよ
Let's fall, let's fall, let's fall, and fall...
ラララ...
...lalala...
おんなじ おんなじ おんなじじゃないか
Are we not all the same, the same, the same?
ラララ...
Lalala...
いけない いけない さみしい さみしい
It's wrong, so wrong, but we're lonely, so lonely.
虎狼来 (Kororon)
[Song: Kororon]
サンタマリア 起死回生の一打を放ってくれ
Santa Maria, please send a comeback miracle to us.
湿っぽいのはいらんな 爽快に派手にやって終い
Free from gloom, give a refreshing, flashy ending.
その答えは自問自答の向こう側にあんだしょうがない
That answer lies beyond our soul searching, it can't be helped.
アンダーグラウンドな世界の中
In this underground world.
井の中の蛙大会優勝者
The champion of the "frog-in-a-well" tournament,
未練たらたら SNSに夢中
...harboring regrets, obsessed with social media.
自尊心なんてとうに無くなって
My self-esteem is already long gone.
愛を謳っては 愛されたことない未体験
Singing of love, a concept I've never experienced.
応えよ 毎度
Answer me, each time...
退場生涯退職生活安泰で居たい
...I wanna quit, I dream of peace and nothing more.
不安などないけれど
Though I have no anxieties,
描いた夢と違うけれど
though it's different from the dream I drew,
何故か心に穴が空いたようだ
for some reason, it feels like there's a hole in my heart,
気付いてしまうから
because I'll end up realizing it.
ありきたりな人生に
To this ordinary life,
今ピリオド打って
I'll put a period now.
外れるようなこの気持ちが 抑えようもない衝動が 望み通り叶わない現実になって
This feeling that seems to derail, this uncontrollable urge, becoming a reality that doesn't go my way,
まだまだくたばってなんか無いぜ
I'm still far from dropping dead.
神に誓って泣いた思い出
The memories of crying while swearing to God,
実態ない将来に宛てていたい
I want to address them to a formless future.
騒ぐココロの音を聴こう
Let's listen to the sound of the stirring heart,
夢の狭間で廃れぬよう
so it won't waste away in the threshold of dreams,
足を止めていられぬよう
so we can't stop our steps,
ころろん 甘いゴースト放とう
Kororon, let's release the sweet ghost.
言葉では何とでも言える 此処が正念場
You can say anything with words; this is the critical moment.
そりゃ外は愛の無いディスカッション 宛てにやってくれ
Well, do those loveless discussions elsewhere.
その結果が全てなんだ 嬉しい誤算か
That result is everything, is it a happy miscalculation?
チャンスは一回だ 脳内生かしてくれよ世界の中
There's only one chance, use your brain in this world.
さあ、ただではないがまだ僕の中には
Now, it's not free, but still inside of me,
数多勝る事の無い真実が
there are truths that cannot be surpassed by many.
虎狼に飼い慣らされるこの毎日が嫌
I hate this daily life of being tamed by beasts,
食べられてしまい
and being eaten up.
実は不安しかないけれど
Actually, I have nothing but anxiety,
描いた夢もないけれど
though I don't even have a dream I drew,
だから心に穴が空いたようだ
that's why it feels like there's a hole in my heart,
気付いてしまった
I've gone and realized it.
ありきたりな人生に
To this ordinary life,
今ピリオド打って
I'll put a period now.
外れるようなこの気持ちが 抑えようもない衝動が 望み通り叶わない現実になって
This feeling that seems to derail, this uncontrollable urge, becoming a reality that doesn't go my way,
まだまだくたばってなんか無いぜ
I'm still far from dropping dead.
神に誓って泣いた思い出
The memories of crying while swearing to God,
実態ない将来に宛てていたい
I want to address them to a formless future.
騒ぐココロの音を聴こう
Let's listen to the sound of the stirring heart,
夢の狭間で廃れぬよう
so it won't waste away in the threshold of dreams,
足を止めていられぬよう
so we can't stop our steps,
ころろん 甘いゴースト放とう
Kororon, let's release the sweet ghost.
Woo! Yay!
Oh, thank you so much for coming, everyone, to my 3D Live!
My name is Ouro Kronii from Hololive English, and we have Sora-senpai!
Yay!
ハロー！ときのそらです、こんそらー！
Hello! I'm Tokino Sora. Kon-Sora!
Yay!
クロニー、ハッピーバースデー！
Kronii, Happy Birthday!
Thank you! Very gorgeous...
Thank you, ありがとうございます！
Thank you, thank you so much!
Oh, man, look at the stage here.
Yeah, very beautiful!
So pretty! Look at the night sky! きれい！
So pretty! Look at the night sky! Beautiful!
Oh, man...
あ、クロニークロニー！
Ah, Kronii, Kronii!
Why did you invite me to your birthday live?
Oh, um... well, last year, um, we hung out together a bit,
and I had a lot of fun. So, I wanted to...
invite you, and, um, get to sing together.
Ah, I thought that would've been really great, so thank you for coming!
Thank you!
Uh, I'm... so, I love you.
Oh, my god! "Love" is such a strong word. Um, I...
I love you, too!
I want to go to, uh, udon eating with...
Oh, udon! Yeah!
Yeah, let's go eat! Oh, my god.
Well, we'll like, we'll get anything. What kind of udon...
I'd like anything!
Yeah, I like anything.
他には？
What else?
Oh, you know, there's like, cold udon...
and then there's just like udon with like soup, and then there's like onsen tamago and like...
色々あるね！
You have quite a variety!
Yeah, yeah, yeah! So like, anything is fine.
あと、一緒にディナー！I'm going to dinner...
Also, let's have dinner together! Let's go to dinner...
Oh, dinner? Yeah! Oh my god, that would be really good!
Yay! Woo!
そう、そう、クロニー、ライブハッシュタグ...
Oh, right! Kronii, the stream hashtag...
Oh yeah! I mean, if you guys haven't already checked it out...
right there, #krorigin!
krorigin? Yeah! Yeah!
And yeah, I hope you guys use this hashtag.
It's going to be awesome, absolute cinema.
And so, yeah, keep on the lookout for Fallen Grace!
Fallen Grace! Woo! Yay!
Thank you so much for coming! 本当にありがとうございました！
Thank you so much for coming! Thank you so much!
こちらこそありがとう！これからは仲良くしてね！
Thank you too! Let's get along from now on!
Yeah! そう言ってもらえて嬉しいです。Yeah!
Yeah! I'm so happy to hear that. Yeah!
大好きなフレンドだから！
Because you're my favorite friend!
Oh my god. Aw, thank you.
じゃあ、またね！Congratulations! Thank you!
See you later! Congratulations! Thank you!
誰が袖に咲く幻花
A phantom flower blooms on the sleeve
ただそこに藍を落とした
I just dropped my indigo dye over there
派手に色を溶かす夜に
On a night when the colors dissolve gaudily
銀朱の月を添えて
with the moon of silver vermillion
転がるように風を切って
Rolling along, breaking through the wind
躓くごとに強くなった
I grew stronger with each stumble
光も痛みも怒りも全部
The light, the pain, and the anger...
抱きしめて
...I hold on to them tightly
選ばれなければ 選べばいい
If you're not chosen, then just choose
声よ轟け 夜のその向こうへ
Let my voice roar out, beyond the night
涙で滲んでた
The landscape so far away,
あんなに遠くの景色まで 響き渡れ
which was blurred by tears, let it resound!
何を奏でて？
What do I want to play?
誰に届けたくて？
Who do I want to deliver it to?
不確かなままでいい
It's okay to be uncertain
どんなに暗い感情も
No matter how dark the feelings,
どんなに長い葛藤も
no matter how long the struggle,
歌と散れ 残響
sing and scatter, reverberation
ただ一人舞う千夜
A thousand nights of dancing alone
違えない帯を結べば
If I tie the same sash
派手な色も負かす様に
As if to beat the gaudy colors,
深紅の香こそあはれ
the fragrance of crimson is all that matters
この先どんなつらい時も
No matter how hard it is in the future,
口先よりも胸を張って
you must put your heart on the line rather than your mouth
抱いた夢の灯りを全部たどるだけ
I'm just trying to follow all the lights of the dreams I hold on to
逃げ出すためここまで来たんじゃないだろ？
I didn't come all this way just to run away, right?
選ばれなければ 選べばいい
If you're not chosen, then just choose
声を枯らして 燃える花のように
Screaming my voice out, like a burning flower,
闇間を照らしたら
if I illuminate the darkness
曖昧過ぎる正解も
Even the most ambiguous answers
譜面にして
I will turn into a musical score
夜を数えて朝を描く様な
To count the nights and paint the morning,
鮮やかな音を鳴らす
let a vivid sound resound!
どんなに深い後悔も
No matter how deep the regret,
どんなに高い限界も
no matter how high the limit,
掻き消して 残響
erase it completely! Reverberation!
In the heavenly realm, there is a Lake of Light that controls all worlds,
and Kronii would always observe the human world from there out of curiosity.
…好奇心から。
...out of curiosity.
好奇心旺盛なクロニーが観察を続けるうちに、
As the curious Kronii continued observing,
天界だけでなく、人間界も訪れてみたいという思いが募っていきました。
a desire grew within her to visit not only the heavenly realm, but also the human world,
人間界で人々と話し、いたずらを仕掛けるために。
where she could talk to people and play tricks on them.
人間界に行ってみたい！
I want to go down to the human world!
ちょっといたずらしてやりたいな。えへへ〜。
I want to play some pranks! Ehehe~
迷子 迷子 真っ只中 さあ
Lost, lost, right in the middle of it,
パッパッパラ パーラ ノーイ ア
pa-pa-para paranoia...
ギコ ギコ my kokoro 剪定
Bzzz-zzzt, pruning my heart,
パッパッパラ パーラ ノーイ ア
pa-pa-para paranoia...
タイロ タイロ ったから又
I ended up looking for an escape route, tangled in
パッパッパラ パーラ ノーイ ア
pa-pa-para paranoia...
sad sad 突っ伏して から
How sad, how sad - collapsed into this
パッパッパラ パーラ ノーイ ド
pa-pa-para paranoia!
さあ バ バ バグ さ バグ バグ
Let's see, it's a bu-bu-bug, a bug, bug;
タ タ タグ 才能 の タグ もう
ta-ta-tag, it's just talents tagged as such,
ハ ハ ハグ 感情 は ハグ
ugh, I'll pe-pe-peel, peel my emotions away,
発症 「 クルシイ 」 は イヤ イヤ イヤ
this onset of "pain" is no good, no good, no good...
イヤ イヤ イヤ
No, no, no!!!
ま、絶叫な感情 落下 パッパラノーイア
Well! I'm emotionally lost amidst all this paranoia!
溺れ声上げては ぐるぐる
I raise my dried-out voice and go round and round.
ま、絶体絶命 落下 やたらめったら
Well! It's a desperate situation, falling headfirst!
沈め 夢々 イヤ イヤ イヤ
Surely, surely sinking, no, no, no!
さあ バ バ バグ さ バグ バグ
Let's see, it's a bu-bu-bug, a bug, bug.
的な外れ ズレ 事態 イヤ イヤ
Your affection is phony, oh how I hate it so!
さあ バ バ バグ さ バグ バグ
Now, it's a b-b-bug you see, bug, bug.
答え 絶え絶え イヤ イヤ イヤ イヤ イヤ イヤ
Answer, stop, stop; I hate it, hate it, hate it!
くるくる パッカン系 ほう、待って無理
Spinny-spin, going insane! Crack! Wait, no way!
ぐるぐる せーので回れ
Spinny-spin, spinning at the count of three!
パッカン系 ほう、やっぱり無理 ぐるぐる アンヨにクサリ
Crack! Yeah, it's no use! Chained up, spinning around!
エンドレス病み
Endless pain...
ダッコ ダッコ いらないコ だ
Squeezed, squeezed tightly, an unwanted child...
パッパッパラ パーラ ノーイ ア
pa-pa-para paranoia...
イイコ イイコ 「ガンバレ」の反乱
Good girl, good girl - making the chat swirl!
アドミニストレーター
Is the administrator... ahh!
さあ バ バ バグ さ バグ バグ
Let's see, it's a bu-bu-bug, bug, bug;
タ タ タグ 才能 の タグ もう
ta-ta-tag, runtime lag...
ハ ハ ハグ 感情 は ハグ
lo-lo-log, a log of rebellion...
発症 「 クルシイ 」 は イヤ イヤ イヤ
bu-bu-bug, pa-ppa-pa-la-pa...
パッパッパグ パッパッパッパパッパパ
pa-pa-pagu, pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa...
パラノイア パラノイア
pa-paranoia, pa-paranoia!
パラノイア イヤ イヤ イヤ
pa-paranoia, no, no, no!
さあ 絶叫な感情 落下 パッパラノーイア
Now then! I'm emotionally lost amidst paranoia!
左右 行き先 も ぐるぐる 悲惨
No matter if I go left or right, all I do is spin - the misery!
限界脳 狂っちゃって やたらめったら
My brain is at its limit, going insane with everything I do!
闇 迷え 迷え いないいないばあ
Lost and intoxicated on this darkness, playing peek-a-boo!
いないいないばってん
Peek-a-boo-hoo, no points for you!
絶叫な感情 落下 パッパラノーイア
I'm emotionally lost amidst all this pa-pa-para paranoia!
溺れ声上げては ぐるぐる
I raise my dried-out voice and go round and round.
ま、絶体絶命 落下 やたらめったら
Well! It's a desperate situation, I'm doomed to fall!
凍え枯れ果て イヤ イヤ イヤ
I'm all frozen over, no, no, no!
さあ バ バ バグ さ バグ バグ
Let's see, it's a bu-bu-bug, now, a bug, bug,
爛れ 荒れ荒れ 悲哀 イヤ イヤ
this sorrow sore and roughened up, I hate it!
さあ バ バ バグ さ バグ バグ
Let's see, it's a bu-bu-bug, now, a bug, bug,
黒まみれ 理性 イヤ イヤ イヤ
all the reason I had is coated in darkness, no, no, no...
今 今 今
Now, now, now...
イヤ イヤ イヤ イヤ イヤ イヤ イヤ イヤ イヤ
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
この世で造花より綺麗な花は無いわ
There's no flower in this world more beautiful than an artificial one,
何故ならば総ては嘘で出来ているわ
because everything is manufactured from lies.
antipathy world
絶望の雨はあたしの傘を突いて 湿らす前髪とこころの裏面
The rain of despair pelts my umbrella and dampens my bangs and the hidden side of my heart.
煩わしいわ
Oh, it's all so troublesome.
何時しか言葉は疾うに枯れきって 事の実があたしに熟れている
Before I knew it, the words had already withered; the fruit of truth is ripening within me.
鏡に映り嘘を描いて 自らを見失った絵画
Painting lies upon the mirror's reflection, a "makeup" of the loss of oneself.
パッパラ パッパ ララッパッパ 謎々 騙して 歌いましょう
Pa pappara pappara rap pappa, let us sing and deceive with riddles.
タタッタラ タッ タラ ラッタッタ 何故 何故 此処が 痛むのでしょう
Tat attarat att ararat tatta, why, oh why, does it hurt here so much?
簡単なことも解らないわ あたしって何だっけ
I can't understand even the simplest of things; what even am I?
それすら夜の手のひらに解されて 愛のように
Even that, unraveled by the hand of the night; just like love...
消える 消える
(it disappears, disappears)
さようなら またねと呟いた フォニイ フォニイ フォニイ
Goodbye, see you later, I murmured; phony, phony, phony.
嘘に絡まっている あたしは フォニイ
Tangled up in lies, I am a phony.
造花だけが知っている秘密の フォニイ
Only the artificial flowers know this secret phony.
antipathy world
何時しか空の音が嫌になりあって
Before we knew it, we grew to hate the sound of the sky,
色の目があなたを溶いている
and prejudice is melting you down.
鏡に映るあたしを欠いて
Lacking the me reflected in the mirror,
誰しもが見間違ったフェイク
everyone mistook me for a fake.
如何して愛なんてものに群がり
Why do we swarm to something like love,
それを欲して生きるのだ今日も
and live our lives desiring it today as well?
泳いでいる夜の電車が通り去っていく
The night train we swim in passes us by...
踊り明かせよ
Dance the night away!
パッパッパラ パッパラ ラッパッパ
Pa-pappara, pappara, rap-pappa,
謎々 騙して歌いましょう
let's sing and deceive with riddles!
タッタッタラ タッタラ ラッタッタ
Ta-ttattara, tattara, rat-tatta,
何故何故 此処が痛むのでしょう
why, oh why, does it hurt here so much?
[Instrumental]
散々な日々は変わらないわ
These miserable days won't change,
絶望の雨は止まないわ
and the rain of despair won't stop.
さよならも言えぬ儘泣いた
I cried, still unable to even say goodbye.
フォニイ フォニイ フォニイ
Phony, phony, phony,
嘘に絡まっている
tangled up in lies.
ただ
Just...
簡単なことも解らないわ
I can't understand even the simplest of things,
あたしって何だっけ
what even am I?
それすら夜の手のひらに絆されて
Even that, bound by the hand of the night...
愛のように消える
disappears like love.
さよならまたねと呟いた
"Goodbye, see you later," I murmured.
フォニイ フォニイ フォニイ
Phony, phony, phony,
嘘に絡まっているあたしはフォニイ
tangled up in lies, I am a phony.
造花だけが知っている秘密のフォニイ
Only the artificial flowers know this secret phony.
Lately, I realized I would never be, never be alone.
It was always right in front of me.
Do you know? Do you remember, remember
how we used to be so carefree?
Oh, hey.
I can feel the rain wash over...
Us, yeah.
Can you hear my heart like thunder?
Upside down, 떨리는 내 목소리
Upside down, my trembling voice.
I've got to make a move, make a move.
So far I could not break through the cage I'm in.
I don't know how to reach for you.
Hardly ever get a chance to speak alone.
Could it ever be, can't you feel it too?
Side by side, we could laugh all through our days.
Baby, just let me make my way to you.
Can't make them stop, hidden sparks inside ignite and flare up.
And when we talk, all my secrets spilling over the top.
So when I step up to your side and my heart is beating in double time,
in every moment you make me feel alive, it goes like:
Oh, hey.
I can feel the rain wash over...
Us, yeah.
Can you hear my heart like thunder?
Upside down, 떨리는 내 목소리
Upside down, my trembling voice.
I've got to make a move, make a move.
So far I could not break through the cage I'm in.
I don't know how to reach for you.
Hardly ever get a chance to speak alone.
Could it ever be, can't you feel it too?
Side by side, we could laugh all through our days.
Baby, just let me make my way to you.
Hardly ever get a chance to speak alone.
Could it ever be, can't you feel it too?
Side by side, we could laugh all through our days.
Baby, just let me make my way to you.
The goddess Kronii's desire to go to the human world and cause mischief grew.
And so, she broke the rules and set foot in the Lake of Light.
The disturbance in the lake drew the attention of the Heavenly Guardians, who seized Kronii and imprisoned her in a cage.
Wait, I haven't done anything yet!
I was just interested in humans and just wanted to talk!
きっと手をつなぐだけでゾッとされる
Surely just holding hands would give them the chills.
馬鹿げた競争抜けたら通報される
If you step out of this foolish rat race, they'll report you.
突然変異じゃない ただの僕さ
I'm no mutant, I'm just myself.
XとかYとか
With all their X's and Y's...
べき論者様は善悪多頭飼い
The moralists keep good and evil like a pack of pets.
僕が君を“侵害”するって言いふらしてる
Spreading rumors that I am "violating" you...
Oh...
Mr.Crazy
Mr. Crazy
ヴィラン ヴィラン
Villain Villain
夜行性の花弁
Nocturnal petals
違う服着て君の前では 男子のフリする
I wear different clothes and pretend to be a boy in front of you
拝啓 Dr.Durand-Durand
Dear Dr. Durand-Durand,
迎えにきて下さい
Please come pick me up
顔も知らない誰かにとって
Even to those I don't know,
僕はもうヴィラン
I'm already deemed a villain
蛇蝎ライフ 蛇蝎ライフ
My hated life, my hated life
挙句の果ての爛
In the end becomes inflamed
逸脱の性をまたひた隠す
Desperately covering up my deviant nature again
雄蕊と雄蕊じゃ立ち行かないの？
Can't get anywhere with stamen and stamen?
ねぇ知ってんのか 乱歩という作家のことを
Hey, do you know a writer called Ranpo?
import you
造花も果ては実を結ぶ
Even artificial flowers will bear fruit someday
ぶるってんじゃねーよ
Don't be so afraid
多種多様の性
There are so many genders
愛しい哀しい話をしようか
Shall we tell gelatinous stories, lovely and miserable ones?
ゼラチン質の
Of gelatinous...
「で？」
"So what?"
Mr.Crazy
Mr. Crazy
ヴィラン ヴィラン
Villain Villain
可能性に幸あれ
All the best to your possibilities
僕のハート 1LDK
My heart's an 1LDK apartment
嫉妬くらいはさせてお
Let me at least be jealous
Hi there もっとYOLO
Hi there, my motto's YOLO, YOLO
微熱愛でいいのに
I'd be fine with just a slightly feverish love...
誰も知らない 知られたくない
Nobody knows and I don't want them to know
皮膚の下
Under my skin
素晴らしき悪党共に捧げる唄
I devote this song to wonderful scoundrels
骨まで演じ切ってやれ悪辣に
Play the role to the bone, viciously
残酷な町ほど綺麗な虹が立つ
The crueler the town, the more beautiful the rainbow
猥雑広告に踊るポップ体の愛
Dancing to vulgar adverts, a pop font love
Mr.Crazy
Mr. Crazy
ヴィラン ヴィラン
Villain Villain
夜行性の花弁
Nocturnal petals
違う服着て君の前では 男子のフリは
I dress differently and pretend to be a boy in front of you
拝啓 Dr.Durand-Durand
Dear Dr. Durand-Durand
ここだよ
I'm right here
顔も知らない誰かにとって
For someone who doesn't know my face,
僕はもうヴィラン
I'm already a villain
蛇蝎ライフ 蛇蝎ライフ
Detested life, detested life
挙句の果ての爛
Eventually corrupting
Man...
I don't know why I'm here. I don't even deserve to be here.
I'm a goddess, I should be treated like one.
Ah... this sucks.
Ugh...
Go away.
La-di-da-di-da-di-da-di-da...
Oh, what nice weather today! Actually, no, I don't know if it's nice weather.
Uh, hello?
Hello.
Hello!
Oh, hello!
Hi!
Hi.
What are you doing here?
You're a beautiful blue woman...
Yeah.
...in a...
...cage?
This doesn't look like a gazebo... It kind of looks like a gazebo at first, but...
Yeah, it's a gazebo.
Uhh...
Well-deserving for a goddess like me, if you can't tell.
Oh yeah! Oh, you're a goddess?
Yeah, I mean, my beauty is pretty telling.
Oh! Well yeah, you know, you're...
...decent.
Decent?!
Yeah! Yeah, I can see it, I can see the...
...yeah, I can see goddess vibes!
What? Okay.
That's a little disrespectful. I've never heard this before.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
Well, I mean, look who you're talking to.
Oh, okay.
Who... who are you? Who do you think you are...
...to be talking...
You don't even deserve to know my name.
What?!
You're in a cage!
Excuse me?
You're like in prison!
No, you just said gazebo! It's not a cage, it's...
No, it's a cage!
It's a gazebo!
If it's a gazebo, then get out of the gazebo then!
I can't!
Why can't you get out of the gazebo?!
Because I'm weak...
...for now.
Oh, you're weak?
Yeah, I need to be protected.
No, you're just bad, like you did something naughty, didn't you?
No, it wasn't even that bad.
Ah, but you did do something bad, and now you're stuck in this...
...gazebo...
...with the dead fly, whatever that is.
Hey!
It may look like a fly, but...
...it's... it's like my moral sup...
You can't talk to it like that.
Why are you talking to a dead fly?
Well, you think I have anyone else to talk to?
You don't deny that it's a dead fly.
It's... I mean...
I mean, what are you? Like, what's that little thing on your head?
It's a halo.
That's different from the halo on the dead fly, okay?!
Maybe you're a fly! Maybe you have wings! What's the difference between you and that thing?
Do I look like a fly?!
Yeah!
I'm not talking to you anymore. You can stay in there, you turnip!
Hey, hold on! Beautiful woman, come back here!
Come back here, yoo-hoo! Hello.
Hello, hello.
Hi.
So, if you happen to open this cage, you can put it on the tab.
Do you even have money?
It can be something else. Something even more valuable.
More valuable than money?!
More valuable than money.
You're not lying to me, are you? / Yeah.
And something that comes with the price of free is...
Guess.
My companionship!
A friend?
Maybe not a friend. I said my companionship.
Goodbye.
Hey, come on! Okay, maybe for a day?
Hello?
For a day?! / For a day, for a day!
For a day? / Yeah.
Now I look like a lonely ass... friendship!
It's okay. It's okay if you're lonely.
You know what, actually, I'm an angel. We should get along.
I am feeling awfully kind right now.
Oh, then maybe you should.
Please beg. If you beg, I'll let you out.
Now, beg.
I'm going to speak to your higher-ups about it.
Well, you can't speak to my higher-ups if you're in this cage.
When I get out of here, you will be fired.
How are you going to get out without me? That's the whole point!
Do you want to take a bet? Do you want to take a gamble or do you want to just free me? You should just free me.
And then maybe I'll beg, or whatever you want.
At the price of my companionship.
I'll free you for... what? I'm here to let you out!
Hey, I don't need you to let me out anymore!
Just beg! It's the magic word... it's just a magic word that starts with a P.
Pray?
Please! Please! Please!
Finally! Finally!
Fine, because I'm so kind. Just one 'please' and it would've been all over.
Okay, let's go.
It's a big door. It's a big door.
Yeah, it is. You got this.
Okay, any day now.
It's okay, I'm a nephilim. I can do this for my beautiful friend, my one-day friend.
Beautiful friend, I will release thee!
Woo!
Wow!
Oh my god, you did it!
Whoa, yay!
Why did I bother? / Yay!
Why did I bother? / Free! Woohoo! We're free! Yeah, let's go!
Good for you.
Give me your hand, please. I need to get down from here.
You can't even let yourself out. Okay.
Thank you very much.
Yeah, that's more like it.
Put you in your place. / Okay, that was really... okay.
You know what? I'll let it slide because you freed me.
Yeah, that's how you show appreciation. / Yeah, well...
I think we should celebrate. Celebrate your freedom? Yeah, yeah!
That's going to be so good. We're going to party.
You're going to treat me to something, right? / I'll treat you to something afterwards.
Okay.
Yeah, and then I'll put a good word in to your higher-ups, and it'll be wonderful.
I don't even have higher-ups. You keep saying I have higher-ups.
You never know. Life is surprising.
Really? / Yeah.
I mean, I'm sure you also have a boss, too, right?
Yay! Yay!
Ow! Ow! Ow! When did you get so strong? Ow.
I've been training recently. Yay! / It shows!
Oh, your hands are so big. / Oh, don't make it weird.
I didn't mean to.
人を過度に信じないように
So as not to over-trust people,
愛さないように期待しないように
not to love them, and not to expect anything.
かと行って角が立たないように
But acting so that you don't cause friction,
気取らぬように目立たぬように
unpretentious and keeping a low profile.
誰一人傷つけぬように
So as not to hurt a single soul,
虐めぬように殺さぬように
not to bully and not to kill.
かと行って偽善がバレないように
But acting so that your hypocrisy isn't exposed,
威張らないように
not to behave overbearingly.
軽いジョークやリップサービスも忘れぬように
Never forgetting light jokes and lip service,
どんな時も笑って愛嬌振りまくように
always smiling and scattering your charms.
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter choco decoration.
兎角言わずにたんまり召し上がれ
No excuses, help yourself to plenty of it.
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter choco decoration.
食わず嫌いはちゃんと直さなきゃ
You really should cure your picky eating habits.
頭空っぽその後に残る心が本物なら
If the heart left behind after emptying your head is real,
きっと君だって同じ事
then surely, you would do the same.
ところで一つ伺いますが先日何処かで？・・・やっぱいっか
"By the way, did we meet somewhere recently?... Actually, never mind."
無駄に自我を晒さぬように
So as not to needlessly expose your ego,
話さぬように分からぬように
not to speak, and not to make sense.
でも絶対口を閉ざさぬように
But make sure to never completely shut your mouth,
笑わすより笑われるように
being laughed at rather than making others laugh.
人をちゃんと敬うように
So as to properly respect others,
崇めるように讃えるように
to revere them and to praise them.
でも決して嫌味にならないように
But make sure it never sounds sarcastic,
ふざけないように
and do not fool around.
集団参加の終身刑
A life sentence of group participation.
またへーこらへーこら言っちゃって
Bowing and scraping, saying "sorry" again...
あれっ前髪ちょーぜつさいきょーじゃん
"Oh, your bangs look absolutely amazing!"
とかどーでもいーの言っちゃって
Saying meaningless things like that.
毎朝毎晩もう限界
Every morning, every night, I'm at my limit.
宗教的社会の集団リンチ
The group lynch mob of a cult-like society,
でも決して発狂しないように
but make sure not to go completely insane.
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter choco decoration.
時に孤独な愛は君を汚す
Sometimes, lonely love will defile you.
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter choco decoration.
立つ鳥の後きっと糞のアート
A departing bird leaves behind art of feces.
初めはあんあ大層な大言壮語を並べたが
At first, you boasted such grand words,
嫌よ嫌よも好きの内
but even "no, no" means "yes" in the end.
いやはやしかし今日が初めてでこんなとはね 君センスあるよ
"My, my, to think it's your first time... you've got good taste."
恋する季節にビターチョコデコレーション
In the season of love, bitter choco decoration.
恋する気持ちでビターチョコデコレーション
With feelings of love, bitter choco decoration.
F.U.C.K.Y.O.U
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter choco decoration.
誰もが望む理想に憧れて
Longing for the ideal that everyone wants,
ビターチョコデコレーション
bitter choco decoration.
心もすべて焼き払い
Burning down every single part of your heart,
ビターチョコデコレーション
bitter choco decoration...
欲やエゴは殺して土に埋め
kill your greed and ego, bury them in the dirt.
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter choco decoration.
僕は大人になりやったよママ
I've finally grown up, Mama.
明日もきっとこの調子の地獄は続くとこまでも
Surely this kind of hell will continue tomorrow, to the end of the earth.
腹からどうか言いたい時は子供の頃の気持ちのままで
When you want to speak from the bottom of your heart, with your childhood feelings...
一緒に戯言やっていこうぜ
Let's spout nonsense together!
思い出したあの時の真面目そうな
I remembered that serious-looking...
やっぱいっか
Actually, never mind.
Oh, thank goodness. Okay. Well, I'm free now.
So I can finally get going. Woohoo!
Yay! Woohoo!
Wait.
I just got out of here!
What's going on?!
Why?!
Don't just stand there, do something!
Ahhhhh!
Ugh...
Oh, what happened?
Oh, what the heck?!
Where are my... where are my beautiful clothes?
What?!
Oh my god!
My... my long, luscious hair!
What happened?!
I can't...
What... what is this? I can't even take it off!
I mean, oh god, at least I still look beautiful, but like...
What happened?!
Oh, man...
I don't know what's going on!
Oh... what is this place, anyway?
いっそ
Well, actually...
[残機 / Lyrics, Music: ACAね]
[Title: Zanki / Lyrics, Music: ACAne]
しょっぱいぜ 初めて嗅いで舐めた出会い
It's salty, what I thought when I smelled it for the first time...
自暴自棄です 平均的な正論が貧乏
It's desperate, but the truth is that we're poor and you're just righteous.
いらっしゃいませ ニンニク増しで目指した健康体
Welcome to this healthy body that you see tonight, with extra garlic...
腹歌満たしてる
filling up my stomach.
優等生 無知なフリして踊っちゃって
Honor student, being ignorant and dancing,
欠陥です 現状把握しちゃうから中断中
it's a defect... now I'm on break, taking time to understand the situation.
もう譲渡 見せびらかし合いましょう 劣等感もう 変えられやしないって分かってるからぁ？
I resigned. Why don't we show off what we have learned? Since we can't change our inferiority complex anyway, right?
直感で自己中な理解不能プレイヤー
A selfish, incomprehensible player moving on pure instinct...
求められたなら三次会
if you ask, it'll just lead to an afterparty.
くだらん口喧嘩でマシになった
Now, what ever could be better than a small squabble?
モットーもっと？ もう意外と辛いのに
Want more? Want more? Even though it's already unexpectedly painful.
うざいくらい叫んだって喰らったって譲れない日々よ
It's annoying how they yell and eat you up on these unyielding days...
栄養になってまた汚し合え
we pick up the pieces and taint each other once again.
残機わかんなくて上がんなくて
I don't care how many lives I have left, I'm not going up.
脊髄反射の涙腺は濁った声で歌えば感謝です
My spinal reflex tear glands are grateful if I sing in a hoarse voice.
試したいわ 温かくて絶対絶命な夜は気持ちいい
I want to try it, this warm and desperate night feels so good...
平穏な生活夢見たいけど
though I want to dream of a peaceful life...
先手必勝が気持ちいいな
winning by making the first move feels amazing.
帰ってすぐに水やり 人間の営み
Watering the plants as soon as I get home, the human routine...
実のところ恵まれても虚無感が友達
even if I am blessed, empty feelings are my friend.
眠気覚まし耳打ち 飲み干すまで合図打ち
Whispering to wake me up, signaling until we drink it all...
仲良しこよしの時間
this friendly and peaceful time.
直感で自己中な理解不能プレイヤー
A selfish, incomprehensible player moving on pure instinct...
求められたなら三次会
if you ask, it'll just lead to an afterparty.
細かいご指摘も有り難き
Even your detailed criticisms are appreciated...
結局瞳孔開いてしまうのに
even though in the end, my pupils end up dilated.
うざいくらい叫んだって喰らったって譲れない日々よ
It's annoying how they yell and eat you up on these unyielding days...
栄養になってまた汚し合え
we pick up the pieces and taint each other once again.
残機わかんなくて上がんなくて
I don't care how many lives I have left, I'm not going up.
脊髄反射の涙腺は濁った声で歌えば感謝です
My spinal reflex tear glands are grateful if I sing in a hoarse voice.
試したいわ 温かくて絶対絶命な夜は気持ちいい
I want to try it, this warm and desperate night feels so good...
平穏な生活夢見たいけど
though I want to dream of a peaceful life...
先手必勝が気持ちいいな
winning by making the first move feels amazing.
ただ穏やかでいたい
I just want to be peaceful.
誰にも迷惑かけたくはないと思うが
I don't want to cause trouble for anyone, but...
戦わないと撫でてもらえない
if I don't fight, I won't get gently patted.
単純明快でした
It was plain and simple.
うざいくらい叫んだって喰らったって譲れない日々よ
It's annoying how they yell and eat you up on these unyielding days...
栄養になってまた汚し合え
we pick up the pieces and taint each other once again.
残機わかんなくて上がんなくて
I don't care how many lives I have left, I'm not going up.
脊髄反射の涙腺は濁った声で歌えば感謝です
My spinal reflex tear glands are grateful if I sing in a hoarse voice.
言い合いたいことジャンケン ご愛顧じゃ
Playing rock-paper-scissors for what we want to say, thanks for your support...
まずは実感湧くまでこしらえ
first, let's prepare until it feels real.
すぐ吐けなくて呆気なくて
I can't throw it up immediately, it's so sudden.
脊髄反射の涙腺は萎んだ脳で歌えば感謝です
My spinal reflex tear glands are grateful if I sing with a shrunken brain.
ダリイシカユイシウスッペライ くだらないことで笑いたかった
It's annoying, itchy, and shallow; I just wanted to laugh at stupid things.
まかないじゃ満たされない不安感
Anxiety that can't be filled with just cheap meals...
暴れるのは疲れるでも侮れない
going wild is tiring, but we can't underestimate it.
傷にはセッションで絶体絶命で健康で気持ちいいな
For wounds, let's have a session, desperate and healthy, it feels so good.
[アイデンティティ / Lyrics, Music: Kanaria]
[Title: Identity / Lyrics, Music: Kanaria]
あ、ちょっと君に伝えたい 何かがあったような
Ah, I want to tell you something, as if something has happened...
けったい真逆の踊るベール サカサマだと知って
a strange, completely reversed dancing veil, knowing it's upside down.
好意とは魅惑のプログラム
Friction is a fascinating program...
ただ差し詰めここから行き着くは愛
in the end, it all leads to love from here.
アイデンティティ それは嗜好のアイデンティティ
Identity, that is the identity of preference.
アイデンティティ 呻れ君一人のせい
Identity, groaning, it's all because of you.
まだ捨てないで待って それは一つ二つのデスティニー
Don't throw it away yet, wait... it's one or two destinies.
繋げてハッピー 落ちる流れ星と歪なあの星
Connect them, happy, falling shooting stars and that distorted star.
重なる面影に寄り添う そっと君に寄り添う
Gently nestling up to the overlapping traces, softly nestling up to you.
はぜだす視界 胸に飛び込む
The bursting sight jumps into my chest.
光るあなたの
...your shining...
アイデンティティ
...identity.
難儀プライド飛び込めデンジャラス
Jump into difficult pride, the dangerous
さっと羽ばたく強気の狂気と
Quickly flapping strong madness
そんで裏切りお涙頂戴
And then, please give me your tears of betrayal
ランブラララと足取りデンジャラス
Dance, la la la, with dangerous footsteps
背後隠れた二人にフォーカス
Focus on the two hidden behind
やっと見つけた不思議な正体
Finally found the mysterious true identity
きっと恋とは真逆のプログラム
Surely love is a reverse program
ただここから差し詰め行き着くは
In the end, it all leads from here...
アイデンティティ それは希望のアイデンティティ
Identity is the identity of hope
アイデンティティ 唸れ 君一人のせい
Identity, groan, it's all because of you
まだ捨てないで待って それは一つ二つのデスティニー
Don't throw it away yet, wait, it's one or two destinies
すぐさまハッピー 落ちる流れ星と歪なあの星
Instantly happy, falling shooting stars and that distorted star
重なる面影に寄り添う そっと君に寄り添う
Gently nestle up to the overlapping traces, nestle up to you softly
弾けだす視界 胸に飛び込むハート
Jump into the bursting sight, your heart...
刻むあなたのアイデンティティ
...carving your identity.
And now, it's time for our special guest to appear!
Wada-mama, please come in!
誕生日おめでとう、クロニー！
Happy Birthday, Kronii!
ありがとうございまーす！
Thank you so much!
I was hoping to have Wada-mama appear at this year's birthday celebration,
so I tried to reach out...
...and she accepted! I'm so happy!
えっと、お母さんが最初来た時は、すごいびっくりしたんだけど、今日はすごいお誕生日の素敵な日なので、
Um, when Mama first came here, I was really surprised, but today is such a wonderful birthday,
ここにこれてとっても嬉しいです。おめでとうございます！
so I'm really happy to be here. Congratulations!
私も嬉しいです！
I'm so happy too!
来てくれてありがとうございます！
Thank you so much for coming!
And, um, since we have this opportunity...
...can I ask Wada-mama some questions?
うん、いいよ。
Sure, go ahead.
Um, like let's say, hmm... what's your favorite food?
あんこです！
Red bean paste!
あんこです。オンリーあんこ。
Red bean paste. Only red bean paste.
Oh, just that? Okay, well...
嘘だけど！
Just kidding!
いっぱいあるけど、あんこが一番好きです。
I have many, but red bean paste is my favorite.
Ah! Okay. I'm gonna keep that in mind for next time.
Um, that's cute. Oh, I have one more question.
What kind of game do you like?
んとね、えっと、RPGと...
Well, um, RPGs and...
んーと、ローグライクのゲームが、好きです。アクションが苦手。
and, um, rogue-like games. I'm bad at action games.
ゲームはですね... でも、簡単なのが好きです。
About games... but, I like simple ones.
Oh, that's nice! And, um...
...oh, yeah! I have some exciting news to share together with Wada-mama!
And please take a look at this! Ta-da!
And we have so much this time too! It's going to be so awesome!
And this illustration was drawn by none other than Wada-mama!
描きました！
I drew it!
She's so talented! Oh my god, I'm so happy!
Um, was there a theme or like a particular detail you focused on for this illustration?
ハッピーのイラストなので、ちょっと派手目に、
Since it's an illustration for a happi coat, I made it a bit flashy,
なんかこう、でっかく、みんなが楽しんで着れるような絵にしました。可愛く描けたと思います！
with a large design so everyone can enjoy wearing it. I think it turned out cute!
It's super cute!
Thank you!
And, um, well, let's go through the details.
First, we have this! Ta-da!
あ、もうハッピって言っちゃった、さっき！
Oh, I already said "happi" earlier!
ごめん、ごめんね。
Sorry, sorry!
It's the Eternal Kronie Happi! And it features a large...
design on the back,
and you can show your support! That'd be so cool!
Woo! Yay! Woo! Ahaha!
And then, we have this next. Tada!
Oh, kawaii!
Oh, so cute!
It's gonna be a Kronii Love! Button Badge!
And... Button badge!
Yay, Kira kira! And it's a heart-shaped, glittery holo...
Yay, sparkly! And it's a heart-shaped, glittery holo...
Whoa, whoa, can badges!
And it's going to be perfect for fan activities,
and you can combine it with the next product, which is this one!
Yay! It's our Oshi Bag! Yay!
And it comes with a clear window where you can display merch,
like maybe a plushie, or like the can badge!
So, keep that in mind! Woohoo!
And then next, we have this!
Oh, kawaii! Yay!
Oh, so cute! Yay!
Um, if you haven't seen already, it's based off of my next... well, not next, my outfit!
Divine Chibi Plushie Keychain!
And it's gonna be so exciting! Yay!
Yay! Yay, yay! Aw.
And then there's a full set purchase bonus!
And, yay!
And the limited quantity includes original card with handwritten signature,
and then the second one is a bonus voice pack called Reminiscence.
And then, don't worry!
Even when those run out, you'll still get...
um, other bonuses like...
original card with foil-stamped replica signature,
and then the voice pack, so don't worry!
And, yeah! Once again, if you want to see the entire summary, here's the full set!
Yay! Yay! Wow!
And then, if you're gonna buy, the full set is...
the way to go, obviously!
And, that's all for our Kronii's birthday!
Woohoo! Yay!
And then, yeah, be sure to buy it, everyone!
And, we have even more news! Whoa! Take a look at this! Woohoo!
Um, so...
the release of my first physical EP, "Way2U,"
has been officially decided!
Sales will start right away after the stream ends,
and the album contains five tracks! Yay!
And this includes "Way2U", "Storm",
"I'm Human Too", "Hibiscus", and...
of course, the classic "Daydream"!
And every song is really special, so I want everyone to listen!
And there's gonna be a CD plus an LP vinyl version,
so maybe you can compare them and see which one you like better!
And, plus it comes with a hand-signed poster,
um, but there's a limited amount, so be sure to check! Yay!
And then, "Way2U" will be released as a...
digital single on 3/15,
which is March 15th, and distribution starts at midnight Japan time tonight,
so don't miss it! Yay!
And, you can check the description for the sales site.
And then, ooh, that was a mouthful!
But, after this, I'd like to sing...
one song together with Wada Mama! Yay!
Yay!
And, I wanted to sing this song ever since I asked, so I'm really looking forward to it!
Yay! So, let's enjoy this! Yay!
Yay!
楽しんでいきましょう！
Let's enjoy this!
ギラギラ (てにをは)
[Giragira - teniwoha]
あーもう本当になんて 素晴らしき世界
Ah, seriously, what a wonderful world!
んで今日もまた 己の醜悪さに惑う
And today, once again, I'm bewildered by my own ugliness.
だのに人を好きって思う気持ちだけは
Yet, the mere feeling of loving someone...
ただの人を好きって思う気持ちだけは
If only the feelings of loving an ordinary person
一丁前にあるから悶えてるんでしょう
were proper, I wouldn't be writhing in agony like this.
UGLY 正直言って私の顔は
UGLY, to be honest, my face
そう神様が左手で描いたみたい
looks like God drew it with His left hand.
必然 この世にあるラブソングはどれ一つ
Naturally, not a single love song in this world
絶対 私向けなんかじゃないでしょう
is meant for someone like me, is it?
使い道のないくちづけ
A useless kiss,
憐みを恵んで欲しいままに
begging for pity, just as I please.
スパンコールの瘡蓋で身を守る
Protecting myself with a sequin scab,
愛されないくらいなんだ
what's the big deal if I'm not loved?
ギラギラ輝いて私は夜を呑み
Gira gira, shining bright, I swallow the night,
Rap tap tap tap 今に見てろこのLuv
Rap tap tap tap, just you watch, this love of mine.
目に染みるは1mgの花火
Stinging my eyes is a one-milligram firework.
Drag on drag on なんてファニー この世はビザー
Drag on, drag on, how funny, this world is bizarre.
Unknown お釈迦様も存ぜぬうちに
Unknown, before even Buddha could notice,
もう健やかに狂っていたみたい
I seem to have gone healthily mad.
それは世界の方か それとも私の方ですか？
Is it the world that's mad, or is it me?
共生は端からムリでしょう
Coexistence was impossible from the very start.
マガイモノこそかなしけれ
How sorrowful indeed is a counterfeit,
無我夢中 疾る、疾る
running, running in a frantic daze.
強い酸性雨が洗い流す前に
Before the heavy acid rain washes it away,
蛍光色の痣抱いて
I'll embrace my fluorescent bruise.
メラメラ火を吹いて私は夜の狼
Mera mera, breathing fire, I am a wolf of the night,
Rap tap tap tap そこで見てろこの乱
Rap tap tap tap, watch from right there, this rebellion.
牙を剥き 抗うの獣で
Baring my fangs, like a resisting beast,
Flag on flag on 不意に不安に孤独アソート
Flag on, flag on, suddenly anxious, an assortment of loneliness.
燃料 火気厳禁な街を行く
Fuel, walking through a highly flammable city.
目を閉じて
Close your eyes.
もう一回 もう一回
One more time, one more time.
もしも神様が左利きなら
If God were left-handed,
どんなに幸せか知れない
I don't know how happy I would be.
ギラギラ輝いて私は夜を呑み
Gira gira, shining bright, I swallow the night,
Rap tap tap tap 今に見てろこのLuv
Rap tap tap tap, just you watch, this love of mine.
目に染みるは1mgの花火
Stinging my eyes is a one-milligram firework.
Drag on drag on なんてファニー この世はビザー
Drag on, drag on, how funny, this world is bizarre.
ギラ ギラ ギラギラ
Gira, gira, gira-gira.
Give love 花は満ちて
Give love, flowers are in full bloom,
ありのままじゃいられない 誰も 誰も
no one can stay just the way they are, no one.
なんて素晴らしい世界だ
What a wonderful world.
ギラついていこう
Let's live life with a sparkle!
This stream depicts events for dramatization and may differ from the official canon.
Fall in Grace / Ouro Kronii Birthday Live 2026
Fall in Grace - Ouro Kronii Birthday Live 2026